One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
We're free!
‫نحن أحرار‬
– Yeah!
‫أجل‬
Bring down Kaido!
‫لنهزم كايدو‬
Hip, hip, hooray!
‫واحد، اثنان، مرحى‬
Luffy!
‫لوفي‬
That was reckless...
‫!يا لتهوّرك‬
Hey.
‫اسمع‬
You gonna fight Kaido again?
‫هل ستقاتل كايدو ثانية؟‬
Wanna join me?
‫أتريد الانضمام لنا؟‬
Don't be stupid!
‫هل أنت أحمق؟‬
Just look at my partner to see how that'll go.
‫...انظر ما فعل بصاحبي‬
Be thankful I don't kill you here and now!
‫اشكرني لأنّني لم أقتلك هنا والآن‬
I'm done with alliances.
‫نلت ما يكفي من التحالفات‬
I can't trust anyone anymore.
‫لن أضع ثقتي بأيّ أحد‬
Let's go, Killer.
‫لنذهب يا كيلر‬
We're gonna get our crew back.
‫لنذهب لاستعادة رفاق طاقمنا‬
It's time we go our own way!
‫سنشقّ طريقنا الخاصّ‬
Warriors' Dream
‫أمنية الجنود‬
Look what twenty years can do.
‫انظر لما تستطيع عشرون سنة فعله‬
Imagine how hard it is to keep believing some pipe dream.
‫مواصلة تصديق حلم متفائل صعبة جدًّا‬
They couldn't even wait ten years...
‫...لم يستطيعوا الانتظار أكثر من عشر سنين‬
They became impatient and advanced on Onigashima.
‫...أمسوا عجولين وقصدوا أونيغاشيما‬
Everyone died!
‫وماتوا جميعًا‬
What in the world happened?!
‫ماذا حدث؟‬
It's been ten years already!
‫مرّت عشر سنين‬
Ten Years Ago
‫قبل عشر سنين‬
We're all getting older.
‫أمسينا شيوخًا‬
If we wait the full twenty years, our vigor will only wane.
‫وسنُمسي أضعف إن انتظرنا عشرين سنة‬
Are we really going to wait for people who may never return?!
‫أتطلب منا انتظار الذين عودتهم مشكوك بها؟‬
Believe in Lady Toki's words...! Believe in the retainers!
‫ضعوا ثقتكم في كلمات توكي-ساما... ثقوا بهم‬
Kin'emon will return!
‫سيعود كينيمون‬
Along with Lord Momonosuke!
‫برفقة مومونوسكي-ساما‬
Since we don't submit to Orochi, we have nothing to eat.
‫ما عدنا نملك ما نسد به جوعنا بما أنّنا لم نخضع لأوروتشي‬
Disease will kill us before a fight does!
‫وسيكون موتنا بسبب المرض لا بالقتال‬
It's Kaido's army!
‫إنّه جيش كايدو‬
What're you doing to the well?!
‫لماذا دمّرت البئر؟‬
Shut up!
‫اخرس‬
We can't take it anymore, Shutenmaru!
‫ما عدنا نتحمّل أكثر يا شوتنمارو‬
You can't! You'll die like dogs!
‫كلاّ، لن يكون لموتكم أيّ مغزى‬
You don't stand a chance without an army under the Kozuki banner!
‫لا فرص لديكم ما لم تشكّلوا جيشًا كبيرًا تحت راية كوزكي‬
We can't take it anymore!
‫ضقنا بهذا الحال ذرعًا‬
At least let us die holding our swords!
‫دعنا نموت حاملين لسيوفنا على الأقلّ‬
If we die, then we do so as samurai!
‫إن كنّا سنموت، نريد الموت كساموراي‬
Please don't stop us!
‫لا توقفنا‬
Do you remember when we were children?
‫...أتذكرون؟ عندما كنّا صبية‬
We had a cry to test our mettle.
‫اعتدنا على الصّراخ بتلك الكلمة واختبار شجاعتنا‬
People place too much value on their own lives, which turns them into cowards!
‫في النّهاية، تقدير قيمة النّفس أكثر من اللاّزم، يجعل المرء جبانًا‬
SNATCH!
‫سوناتشي‬
Surrender Names And Thoughts;
‫تخلّوا عن أسمائكم، تخلّوا عن أذهانكم‬
Cease Hesitations! Then take the plunge!
‫اقفزوا دونما أيّ تفكير معمّق‬
That's what our yell meant!
‫هذا ما تعنيه تلك الكلمة‬
Raise your voices! SNATCH!
‫فليصدح صراخكم، سوناتشي‬
– SNATCH! SNATCH! SNATCH!
‫سوناتشي‬
Don't do this!
‫توقّفوا‬
If we die, then we do so as samurai!
‫إن كنّا سنموت، نريد الموت كساموراي‬
– SNATCH! SNATCH! SNATCH!
‫سوناتشي‬
Why did we need to wait twenty years?
‫لماذا استغرق الأمر عشرين سنة؟‬
We'll know once it's over!
‫سنعرف ذلك بمجرّد انتهائه‬
There must be a reason.
‫لا بدّ من مغزى لكلّ هذا‬
I have no reason to doubt Lord Oden.
‫لا سبب يدفعني لأشكّك بأودين-ساما‬
Hey! Men!
‫يا رجال‬
In eight days,
‫...بعد ثمانية أيام‬
on the night of the fire festival,
‫في ليلة مهرجان النّار‬
we will raid Onigashima under the Kozuki banner
‫...سنغير على أونيغاشيما باسم كوزكي‬
to take the pirate Kaido and the Shogun Orochi's heads!
‫لندقّ عنقيْ القرصان كايدو والشّوغن أوروتشي‬
If you're willing,
‫من ما زال منكم عازمًا‬
follow me!
‫فليتبعني‬
– Yeah!
‫أجل‬
Of course we will, Boss! We've been waiting a long time for this day!
‫بالطّبع سنتبعك يا زعيم، انتظرنا هذا اليوم بفارغ الصّبر‬
Ashura!
‫أشورا‬
You guys haven't aged since that day, huh?!
‫لم تتغيّروا قطّ مذّاك اليوم، صحيح؟‬
We were once the same age, but now we're twenty years stronger!
‫كنّا في نفس العمر حينها، لكن بعد أن عشنا عشرين سنة أطول منكم، صرنا أقوى منكم‬
Right, you old dog?!
‫أليس كذلك أيها الكلب؟‬
Yes, indeed!
‫نعم، معك حقّ‬
Silence, old timers! Do not get in our way!
‫اخرسا أيّها العجوزان، لا تعترضا طريقنا‬
Why, you whelp...!
‫أيّها الشّقيّ الغرّ‬
Whoa, cut it out! We won't be able to break up a fight among the Red Scabbards!
‫!مهلًا، مهلًا، توقّفوا! لا أحد بمقدرته إيقاف قتال بين الأغماد‬
Udon
‫أودون‬
A pirate?!
‫قرصان؟‬
That straw hat guy is a pirate just like Kaido?!
‫ذو قبّعة القشّ قرصان مثل كايدو؟‬
Yes, but he is different!
‫نعم، لكنّه مختلف‬
He's untrustworthy! He'll betray us for sure!
‫!لا يمكننا أن نثق به! واثقون أنّه سيخوننا‬
For crying out loud, why would you bring a damn pirate?!
‫لماذا أحضرتم قرصانًا من بين الجميع؟‬
Look, the seas are vast, with all sorts of pirates...
‫حسنٌ، العالم واسع وثمّة أنواع مختلفة من القراصنة‬
That man is key to defeating Kaido!
‫ذلك الرّجل ضروريّ للإطاحة بكايدو‬
Why do we need a pirate?!
‫أنّى لنا أن نثق به؟‬
Oh no, we must have missed something. Everyone's regained their senses, and yet...
‫...هذا سيّئ، نفتقر لشيء ما، لقد عادوا لرشدهم، ولكن‬
First of all, did you really come from twenty years in the past?
‫أوّلًا، هل صحيح أنّكم أتيتم من الماضي قبل عشرين سنة؟‬
Raizo, you've always looked old.
‫رايزو-سان، طالما بدوت أكبر من عمرك‬
How do we know you haven't just naturally aged twenty years?
‫لذلك لا يمكننا معرفة إن كبرت عشرين سنة أم لا‬
Even unintentionally, you insult me!
‫ربّما لم يكن هذا مقصدكم لكنّكم تجرحون مشاعري‬
Where is Sir Straw Hat?
‫أين ذهب فتى قبّعة القشّ؟‬
Tama, it's dangerous for you to be here.
‫ما كان عليك المجيء يا تاما، المكان خطير هنا‬
Forgive me, Big Bro.
‫أعتذر يا أخي الكبير‬
But I'm so glad you're okay!
‫لكنّني مسرورة لأنّك بخير‬
Yeah...
‫...نعم‬
He's on death's door.
‫يبدو لي على شفير الموت‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟ -‬
B-Big Bro, you've gotta be strong!
‫يا أخي الكبير، تشجّع‬
Don't touch him!
‫لا تلمسيه‬
I'll find the antibodies soon enough.
‫سأعثر على التّرياق قريبًا‬
You shouldn't have pretended that it doesn't hurt!
‫ما كان عليك أن تتظاهر أنّه لا يؤثّر فيك‬
Painful, isn't it?! Why couldn't you have considered the consequences?!
‫لا بدّ أنّك تعاني، لماذا لا تفكّر قبل أن تتصرّف؟‬
Tell me you're sorry!
‫عليك أن تعتذر لي‬
I'm sorry.
‫أعتذر‬
It's painful.
‫أنا أتألّم‬
Help me.
‫ساعدني‬
Hang on.
‫انتظر فحسب‬
We don't need no damn pirates!
‫لا حاجة لنا بالقراصنة‬
Get him out of here!
‫اطردوهم‬
Luffy, as dumb as you are, you sure are amazing.
‫قد يكون لوفي غبيًّا، لكنّه مميّز‬
I could never do something like that.
‫ما كنت لأفعل شيئًا كالّذي فعله‬
Momo, you...
‫...مومو، إنّك‬
are a real idiot...
‫...غبيّ حقيقيّ‬
and a coward...
‫...وجبان‬
and a weakling...
‫...وضعيف‬
and a wimp...
‫...وواهن‬
You're just hopeless.
‫لا أمل يُرجى منك‬
Shut up, you insolent dog!
‫اخرس، أنت فظّ جدًّا‬
You have no right to speak to me like that!
‫لا يحقّ لك بتاتًا التّحدّث معي هكذا‬
Momo, don't hit him!
‫مومو-كُن، لا تلمسه‬
What are you, a chicken?
‫ماذا تكون؟ جبان؟‬
I am Kozuki Momonosuke.
‫...أنا كوزكي مومونوسكي‬
The son of Kozuki Oden!
‫ابن كوزكي أودين‬
Then get out there, Momo!
‫اذهب إذًا يا مومو‬
Banish the pirate!
‫اطردوهم‬
Go already!
‫اذهب بسرعة‬
S-Stop, you fool! Do you intend to kill me?!
‫تـ-توقّف أيّها الأبله، هل ستقتلني؟‬
Who do you think they're waiting for?
‫من ينتظرون في رأيك؟‬
They're waiting for you!
‫إنّهم في انتظارك أنت‬
Is that...? Could it be?
‫...أيعقل... أنّه‬
Lord Momonosuke!
‫مومونوسكي-ساما‬
Thank goodness you're alive!
‫كم أنا شاكر لأنّك حيّ‬
I see now.
‫...صحيح‬
What was missing...
‫...ما كنّا نفتقر له‬
was a dream.
‫هو حلم‬
A future... after the war.
‫ما ينتظرنا بعد هذه المعركة‬
It's not me.
‫...ليس أنا‬
Certainly all they are seeing is my father...
‫...أظنّ أنّ ما يراه الجميع هو والدي‬
the huge shadow cast by the Kozuki that upheld Wano.
‫ظلّ كوزكي العظيم الّذي حمى بلاد وانو‬
I-I cannot do it...
‫...لا-لا أستطيع‬
I cannot!
‫لا أستطيع‬
I want to defeat Kaido!
‫أريد الإطاحة بكايدو‬
Momonosuke...
‫مومونوسكي‬
Do not be afraid, Momonosuke...
‫...لا تخف يا مومونوسكي‬
Do not be afraid, Momonosuke!
‫لا تخف يا مومونوسكي‬
Everyone!
‫أيها الجمع‬
Please hear me!
‫أنصتوا إلي‬
What happened that fateful day at Oden Castle?
‫...ما حدث في قلعة أودين يومها‬
Kin'emon, Raizo, Kanjuro, and I embarked on a quest for allies.
‫ذهبت في رحلة للبحث عن حلفاء رفقة كينيمون والبقيّة‬
However, I became separated from them in a dangerous place with no way out.
‫لكنّني انفصلت عنهم وتعثّرت عاجزًا في مكان خطير‬
I could only return here with the aid of Luffy and his friends, whom we met along the way.
‫...لعجزتُ عن العودة دون مساعدة لوفي والآخرين الّذين قابلتهم في الطّريق‬
I am still not strong enough...
‫لستُ قويًّا كفايةً بعد‬
but I promise to avenge everyone, no matter the cost!
‫لكنّني سأثأر للجميع بأيّ ثمن‬
Even through trying times, I carried on and never gave in...
‫...حتّى في الأوقات العصيبة أستطيع المواصلة دونما استسلام‬
for the sake of one wish.
‫بسبب أمنية واحدة‬
To fulfill that wish, I need like-minded allies...
‫...ولتحقيقها، أحتاج حلفاء من نفس الطّينة‬
I need the help of all like-minded citizens of Wano!
‫أحتاج مساعدتكم جميعًا يا أهل وانو‬
We all share one wish!
‫نتشارك جميعنا أمنية واحدة‬
To take back Wano!
‫ألا وهي استعادة بلاد وانو‬
I owe all of you my gratitude,
‫أيّها النّاس... طوال السّنوات العشرين الماضية‬
waiting for us to arrive after two decades!
‫انتظرتمونا وأنا أشكركم على ذلك‬
I am the heir to a daimyo of Wano.
‫...أنا وريث منصب دايميو بلاد وانو‬
I am Kozuki Momonosuke!
‫كوزكي مومونوسكي‬
Now is the time to rise up!
‫آن الأوان لننهض‬
– Yeah!
‫أجل‬
Lord Momonosuke's courage sets my heart at ease.
‫أراحتني معرفة أنّ مومونوسكي-ساما قد صار أقوى‬
I have an urgent matter to attend to. I promise to join you all before the battle.
‫ثمّة مكان عليّ أن أقصده بشكل طارئ، أعد أن أنضمّ لكم قبل المعركة‬
I see. Understood.
‫حسنًا، مفهوم‬
You bastard...
‫...سُحقًا لك‬
Is this all of them?
‫أهذا كلّ شيء؟‬
How many are there? It's a damn ninja army.
‫كم يوجد هنالك من نينجا؟‬
Are you injured?
‫هل أنت بخير؟‬
I'm fine.
‫أنا على ما يرام‬
I apologize. I have been a burden.
‫...اعذرني لعرقلتك طريقك‬
You have.
‫...نعم‬
But don't worry about it.
‫حسنًا، لا داعي للقلق‬
If you died, I could never show my face to Momonosuke again.
‫ما كنتُ لأستطيع مواجهة مومونوسكي إن قُتلتِ‬
Enma Shrine Deep in a Forest
‫معبد إنما في أعماق الغابة‬
We're heading back to that house in the snow, right?
‫تريدين العودة للمنزل في المنطقة الثّلجيّة، صحيح؟‬
As long as I can hide, anywhere is fine.
‫لا يهمّ ذلك ما دمت أستطيع إخفاء نفسي‬
I want to go back to where that guy took my sword.
‫أريد العودة للرّجل الّذي سرق سيفي‬
I will gladly show you the way. Bandit's Bridge in Ringo, correct?
‫سأرشدك إليه بالطّبع، كان في جسر قطّاع الطّرق في رينغو، صحيح؟‬
I need my missing sword before the battle...
‫من الضّروريّ أن أستعيده قبل المعركة الكبيرة‬
otherwise my waist won't feel right.
‫لا أشعر بالرّاحة دونه‬
I guess I made Orochi really mad...
‫...أظنّني أغضبتُ أوروتشي كثيرًا‬
It's no wonder our pursuers are relentless.
‫فرقة المطاردة خاصّته مزعجة جدًّا‬
Otoko... Do you think she'll be okay?
‫...أتساءل إن كانت أوتوكو بخير‬
Yasuie!
‫ياسويي‬
Daddy!
‫أبي‬
After such tragedy befell her father...
‫...بعد ذلك الفِعل الشّنيع الّذي حدث لوالدها‬
I am worried I could not be there for her.
‫...أنا قلقة لأنّني عجزتُ عن مساندتها‬
I left her with my crew.
‫إنّها مع طاقمي‬
She's at least safe from harm.
‫...ستكون بخير، جسديًّا على الأقلّ‬
I'll never forgive Orochi!
‫لن أغفر لأوروتشي أبدًا‬
I will avenge Tonoyasu, no matter what it takes.
‫سأثأر لتونوياسو بأيّ ثمن‬
I would like... nothing more...
‫...أتمنّى... لو أستطيع‬
than to kill him myself!
‫قتله بنفسي‬
You did what?!
‫ماذا قلت؟‬
You let them get away?!
‫سمحت لهما بالهرب؟‬
And the ronin who attacked me?!
‫ماذا عن الرّونين الّذي هاجمني؟‬
I am terribly sorry...
‫...أنا أعتذر‬
I am disappointed in you guys!
‫كنت أنت وفرقة النينجا الخاصة بك هناك‬
We did capture the man called Trafalgar.
‫لكنّنا قبضنا على رجل يُدعى ترافالغار‬
Tra... falgar?
‫ترا... فالغار؟‬
Who the hell is that?!
‫و من يكون؟‬
He is a ringleader alongside Straw Hat.
‫إنّه واحد من عقولهم المدبّرة تمامًا مثل قبّعة القشّ‬
It means we have captured the two leaders of the invaders.
‫إذًا أمسى اثنان من قادة مجموعة الدّخلاء في قبضتنا‬
Where is he now?!
‫أين هو الآن؟‬
In the world of pirates, betrayal never goes out of style!
‫إنّ رياح الخيانة لا تكفّ عن الهبوب في عالم القراصنة‬
Even after torturing him, we can use him in so many ways.
‫حتّى بعد تعذيبنا له، بإمكاننا استغلاله بطرق عدّة‬
That sounds good.
‫يبدو ذلك جيّدًا‬
So, how is the capital?
‫ما وضع العاصمة؟‬
Please rest assured.
‫لا داعي للقلق‬
Currently, the city is on high alert,
‫إنّها في حالة تأهّب عالية‬
with samurai and ninja on patrol throughout the city.
‫ونشرنا دوريّات من قوّات السّاموراي والنّينجا في كلّ أرجائها‬
Until we capture all the invaders,
‫وإلى أن يُقبض على كلّ الدّخلاء‬
I shall abide no attempt on your life, Lord Orochi.
‫فسأحرص كلّ الحرص على حمايتك جيّدًا‬
If you see any of these people, report them immediately.
‫أبلغوا عن الأمر في الحال إذا ما رأيتم أيًّا من هذه الوجوه‬
These are all wanted posters?!
‫كلّ هذه ملصقات مطلوبين؟‬
Know that any attempt to ignore or conceal them will bring conspiracy charges!
‫اعلموا أنّ السّماح لهم بالهرب أو إخفائهم سيُعدّ تآمرًا‬
We're in a bad spot...
‫...يا إلهي‬
We can't go anywhere near the capital anymore.
‫سيكون علينا البقاء بعيدين عن العاصمة حاليًّا‬
Not just the capital! Those posters are all over the country!
‫ليس العاصمة فحسب، نحن مطلوبون في كلّ البلاد‬
Still, in some respect, our job is done in the capital.
‫لكنّ شأننا في العاصمة قد تمّ بطريقة ما‬
Our objective was to find all the samurai with the crescent tattoos.
‫كان هدفنا هو إيجاد السّاموراي الحاملين لوشم الهلال‬
But all those samurai are...
‫...لكنّ كلّ أولئك السّاموراي‬
...behind bars now.
‫خلف القضبان الآن‬
Release us immediately!
‫أخرجونا من هنا في الحال‬
Keep quiet!
‫اخرسوا‬
Tonoyasu's swan song was meant to convince Orochi that those samurai were innocent.
‫ظننتُ أنّهم سيُعدون أبرياء بعد إلقاء تونوياسو لذلك الخطاب مخاطرًا بحياته‬
Indeed, but it is not as simple as that.
‫قد لا يكون الأمر بهذه السّهولة‬
The prisoners' quarters are vast. I estimate about a thousand people were caught.
‫مقرّ السّجناء واسع، أفترض أسرَ ألفًا منهم‬
Hey, why aren't they releasing these guys?
‫لماذا لم نحررهم بعد؟‬
Do you think Lord Orochi would own up to a mistake?
‫أتظنّ أنّ أوروتشي-ساما سيقول "إنّني مخطئ"؟‬
He would never admit to his own blunder.
‫لن يعترف أنّه أخطأ أبدًا‬
You're right.
‫أنت محقّة‬
But now we know that they're our allies...
‫...لكنّنا بتنا نعرف الآن أنّهم حلفاؤنا‬
We need them! We have to do something!
‫إنّنا في أمسّ الحاجة لعونهم، من واجبنا فعل شيء حيال ذلك‬
Law's crew should be in there too.
‫طاقم لاو موجود هناك أيضًا‬
By the way, Shinobu... What're they doing down there?
‫بالمناسبة يا شينوبو-تشان، ماذا يفعلون؟‬
Ah, they're making sky boats.
‫صحيح، إنّهم يصنعون قوارب سماء‬
Sky boats?
‫قوارب سماء؟‬
It's in preparation for the upcoming Fire Festival.
‫إنّ مهرجان النّار وشيك فإنهم يحضرون له‬
Two of their icons just died. It's hard to believe they'd put on a festival.
‫فقدوا شخصين مهمّين، أراهن أنّهم ليسوا في مزاج للاحتفال‬
Actually, it's just the opposite.
‫كلاّ، على العكس تمامًا‬
The Flower Capital's Fire Festival is an occasion to honor the dead.
‫إنّ مهرجان النّار في عاصمة الزّهور هو حدثٌ لتكريم الأموات‬
The more momentous the festivities, the more our thoughts go out to the departed.
‫كلّما كان المهرجان أضخم كانت فرص بلوغ مشاعرنا للأموات أكبر‬
Oh? So this festival is pretty important...
‫إنّه مهرجان مهمّ لهم إذًا‬
North of Ebisu Town Outskirts of the Flower Capital
‫شمال بلدة إيبيسو بضواحي عاصمة الزهور‬
I'm glad you're safe!
‫أنا سعيدة لأنّكم أحياء‬
Yeah, sorry to make you worry...
‫...نعم، نعتذر على إقلاقكم‬
I heard you all were captured.
‫سمعتُ أنّكم قد أُسرتم‬
We were lucky enough to get away.
‫لحسن الحظّ أنّنا هربنا -‬
Great!
‫جيّد -‬
Oh, that's right!
‫مهلًا، صحيح‬
Take a look at this...
‫...ألقوا نظرة على هذه‬
Before he died, a daimyo named Yasuie...
‫...قبل موته، قام دايميو يُدعى ياسويي‬
What?! Yasuie?!
‫ماذا؟ ياسويي؟‬
While in prison, he drew this symbol and showed it to all the inmates!
‫برسم هذا الرّمز وأراه لمن كانوا في السّجن‬
Wait a minute...
‫...مهلًا لحظة‬
The snake has two added lines...?
‫ثمّة خطّان إضافيّان للأفعى؟‬
Yeah, that's right!
‫نعم، هذا صحيح‬
I guess that changes the meaning of the code.
‫أظنّ أنّ المقصود من الرّمز قد تغيّر بهذين الخطّين‬
Those from Wano understood what it meant.
‫عرف شعب بلاد وانو المقصود منه‬
It's Yasuie's final message.
‫إنّها رسالة ياسويي الأخيرة‬
This is vital!
‫هذا في غاية الأهمية‬
I'll be sure to pass it on to Kin'emon!
‫سأحرص على تبليغها لكينيمون‬
Yes, please do!
‫أعتمد عليك‬
Okay!
‫أكيد‬
Come to Amigasa Village if you need us.
‫تعالوا إلى قرية أميغاسا إن احتجتم للمساعدة‬
Okay! Give our regards to the others!
‫أكيد، بلّغي سلامنا للبقيّة‬
Captain...
‫...أيّها القبطان‬
Captain!
‫أيّها القبطان‬
Your lives are the terms of our exchange.
‫كانت حياتكم هي ورقة مساومته‬
"Our exchange"? What does that mean?!
‫مساومة"؟ ماذا تعني بذلك؟"‬
Should I refuse, then Trafalgar Law...
‫...إن رفضتُ، فإنّ ترافالغار لاو‬
will come for my life, thus sacrificing yours.
‫سيسلبني حياتي إلى جانب حياتكم‬
A threat from a man unwilling to bet on tomorrow...
‫...تهديد من رجل غير عازم على المراهنة بالغد‬
is something that raises concern for my own life.
‫لهو أمر يُثير القلق حيال حياتي أنا‬
Captain, we're sorry! We screwed up!
‫نعتذر أيّها القبطان، إنّها غلطتنا‬
These three lives belong to you!
‫هذه هي حيواتكم أنتم الثّلاثة‬
You're completely free.
‫...أنتم أحرار بالكامل‬
Any objections, Trafalgar?
‫ليست لديك أيّ مشكلات، صحيح يا ترافالغار؟‬
No, you can't!
‫كلاّ، كلاّ‬
Don't go! Captain!
‫لا تذهب أيّها القبطان‬
Listen, guys.
‫أصغوا يا رفاق‬
You can never tell the Straw Hat or anyone else that I got caught.
‫إيّاكم أن تخبروا قبّعة القشّ-يا والبقيّة أنّني أُسرت‬
What...? Wh-Why not?!
‫ماذا؟ لماذا؟‬
Captain!
‫أيّها القبطان‬
Wait!
‫انتظر‬
Please don't go!
‫لا تذهب‬
Captain!
‫أيّها القبطان‬
I'm sorry...
‫...أعتذر‬
Everyone... because we messed up...
‫...يا رفاق... بسبب غلطتنا‬
Captain is...!
‫...القبطان‬
We can't just sit around waiting!
‫لا يمكننا الجلوس مكتوفي الأيدي‬
We're the Heart Pirates!
‫إنّنا قراصنة القلب‬
Let's take our captain back!
‫لنستعد قبطاننا‬
His life is more important than Kin'emon's plan!
‫حياة قبطاننا أهم من خطّة كينيمون‬
Trafalgar Law!
‫ترافالغار لاو‬
You bastard...
‫وغد‬
Leave it at that.
‫هذا أكثر من كافٍ‬
What's wrong? You've been acting strangely.
‫ما الخطب؟ أنت تتصرّف بغرابة‬
It's nothing.
‫لا، ما من خطب‬
Let's make this quick.
‫لننه هذا الأمر‬
Yeah, it's an easy job.
‫صحيح، إنّها مسألة سهلة‬
We'll be done as soon as you sing.
‫سينتهي الأمر بمجرّد أن تفصح بما لديك‬
Your crew is allied with the Straw Hats.
‫ثمّة اتّفاق بين طاقمه وطاقم قبّعة القشّ‬
What could you all possibly be planning here in Wano?
‫ما الغاية الّتي أتت بكم إلى بلاد وانو؟‬
Tell us everything.
‫أخبرنا بكلّ شيء‬